<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Linux Documentation on My Homelab Notes</title>
    <link>https://vincat.github.io/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Linux Documentation on My Homelab Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:25:45 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vincat.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Basics</title>
      <link>https://vincat.github.io/basics/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:43:40 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vincat.github.io/basics/index.html</guid>
      <description>Hugo This will be my notes on getting Hugo up and running on Ubuntu, and then publishing on Github pages.
Below is a series of commands to install Hugo and then create your first site.
Then cd into directory, pick a theme from Hugo Themes, following the themes directions for installation.
sudo snap install hugo hugo version hugo new site Hugo1 cd ./Hugo1 git submodule add https://github.com/theNewDynamic/gohugo-theme-ananke.git themes/ananke echo &amp;#34;theme = &amp;#39;ananke&amp;#39;&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; hugo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homelab</title>
      <link>https://vincat.github.io/homelab/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:25:45 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vincat.github.io/homelab/index.html</guid>
      <description>This section will contain my notes and configuration files on my home lab.
Environment As you can see from the picture, we are not talking about some powerful, power hungry set up.
For the home user with modest requirements, i.e less than 4 users, then not much more than what is displayed in the image is all you will need.
I have 3 HPEliteDesktop, and a bunch of Raspberry PI&amp;rsquo;s, not all running at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command Line</title>
      <link>https://vincat.github.io/command-line/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 09:09:41 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vincat.github.io/command-line/index.html</guid>
      <description>This chapter will be my notes on using the command line on Linux, specifically Ubuntu.
Most of the content here should work in any Linux distribution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://vincat.github.io/about/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vincat.github.io/about/index.html</guid>
      <description>I love technology.
But, sometimes technology does not love me!
This site will be my public notes about Linux/Homelab experiences.
Hopefully you find it helpfull.
Contact Please consider leaving feedback, suggestions etc &amp;hellip;
vincent@vincat.blog</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>